midnightbox.com 2008-09-12

# MidnightBox.com :: Privacy Policy

* * *

## Page Content

At MidnightBox.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy online. Our Privacy Policy demonstrates our firm commitment to protecting the privacy of our customers. We use the information that we collect about our customers to fulfill product and service purchases and to create a more personalized online experience.

When you shop at MidnightBox.com, we collect transactional information, or Personally Identifiable Information, from you such as your name, telephone number, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, credit card or other payment information and a password. MidnightBox.com does not sell or rent your transactional information to others without your prior consent. MidnightBox.com uses customer information only for the purposes of filling orders, contacting purchasers to inform them of their order status, sending promotional information, and enhancing the user experience.

MidnightBox.com uses cookies to help identify you when you visit the site. The cookies make your use of the site easier, allow you to retrieve an earlier shopping cart, make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site. Cookies MUST be enabled on your system to shop at MidnightBox.com.

MidnightBox.com will occasionally offer special contests and promotions. When you enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask you for contact information such as your name, address and e-mail address in order to administer the contest, to send you promotional e-mails, notify winners and make the winners' list publicly available pursuant to certain states' laws. Your consent to such promotional use and disclosure of this information is a condition of your participation.

At MidnightBox.com you can be assured that your transactional information is secure, consistent with current industry standard SSL encryption technology. The importance of security for all transactional information associated with our customers is of utmost concern to us. Our secure servers protect the information using state of the art firewall technology. All customer transactional account information is kept on a secure server.

Please be aware that our site may contain advertisements and links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. The information practices of those websites linking from or to our site are not covered by the MidnightBox.com Privacy Policy. MidnightBox.com has no control over the use or disclosure of user data on other sites on the Internet and we recommend that you review the privacy policies of such sites to determine your privacy rights on such sites.

MidnightBox.com will remain committed to protecting your privacy online. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. When such a change is made, we will post the revised Privacy policy on our website so please bookmark this page and check back periodically. Any changes, corrections or updates to your transactional information can be edited during the purchase process. If you have questions regarding the MidnightBox.com Privacy Policy, please contact us.

* * *

| 

## User Account Info

#### Past Boxes

  * September, 10 2008, 12:00 AM EDT
  * September, 9 2008, 12:00 AM EDT
  * September, 8 2008, 12:00 AM EDT
  * September, 7 2008, 12:00 AM EDT
  * September, 6 2008, 12:00 AM EDT
  * September, 5 2008, 12:00 AM EDT

#### Syndication

  *
